http://www.gilmoreandgilmore.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

December 11, 2020
Posts
Comments
Gilmore and Gilmore Professional CorporationGood lawyers, full service, friendly staffHome
Privacy Policy
Gilmore and Gilmore maintains a strict privacy policy and is committed to protecting your personal information. Gilmore and Gilmore has implemented this privacy policy to let you know exactly how and when we will use any personal information that we may collect from you. We promise that we will only use your personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.
This privacy policy complies with the terms of the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.
During the course of communicating with you we will need to collect certain personal information which we require to interact effectively with you as well as complete any work you hire us to do on your behalf. In accordance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act we are required to inform you as to what will happen to the information we collected. Your personal information (i.e. dates of birth, address, financial information) will remain in our files and cannot be accessed by third parties as our files are stored under secure conditions and will only be released upon your specific instruction. Your information will remain in our computer system unless you specifically ask us to remove it. Our computers are password protected and accessible only by the firm partners and our trusted employees. We retain this information in our computer system only for ease of reference in the event we are required to contact you about your file in future or in the event you wish us to act for you again. The information is never given to third parties. You may contact our Privacy Co-ordinator, Jamie Gilmore, if you have any questions about your personal information.
If we should discontinue our practice of law (we do not anticipate doing that at any time in the foreseeable future), we may pass this information on to any succeeding lawyer or lawyers who will use it for purposes similar to these.
We may use this information for the purpose of contacting you in the future to advise you of any changes or developments in the law that might be relevant to you or to inquire as to whether we may be able to assist you with any of your legal work or needs from time to time. We may also use this information for the purpose of sending you general or specific information on issues that may be relevant to you or for the purpose of personal communication.
CONTACT US
Feel free to contact us at any point for assistance or advice. We may be reached at 705-435-4339 / 1-877-85LEGAL (1-877-855-3425) or contact us via email .
About Us
Gilmore & Gilmore Professional Corporation established in 1986 has offices in Toronto and Alliston, Ontario, Canada. We are specialists in Wills, Powers of Attorney, Estate Law, Estate Litigation and offer extensive Estate Administration Services. Our Real Estate team handles a broad range of deals with a strong reputation for handling complex situations quickly and effectively.
Read More
Home
About Us
Our Lawyer
Our Support Staff
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Areas of Practice
